Welcome to the world.
Sorry, Baby is a drama, comedy film directed by Eva Victor.
Agnes feels stuck.
Unlike her best friend, Lydie, who’s moved to New York and is now expecting a baby, Agnes still lives in the New
England house they once shared as graduate students, now working as a professor at her alma mater.
A ‘bad thing’ happened to Agnes a few years ago and, since then,
despite her best efforts, life hasn’t gotten back on track.
Agnes, played by Eva Victor.
Lydie, played by Naomi Ackie.
Preston Decker, played by Louis Cancelmi.
Natasha, played by Kelly McCormack.
Gavin, played by Lucas Hedges.
Pete, played by John Carroll Lynch.
Sorry, Baby is a 2025 American black comedy-drama film written and
directed by Eva Victor, in their directing debut.
Starring Victor, Naomi Ackie, Louis Cancelmi, Kelly
McCormack, Lucas Hedges, and John Carroll Lynch.
The film follows a reclusive college literature professor
struggling with depression following a sexual assault.
The film had its world premiere at the 2025 Sundance Film Festival on January 27, where it won
the Waldo Salt Screenwriting Award and received widespread critical acclaim.
It was released by A24 in selected theaters in the United States on
June 27, before expanding nationwide on July 25.
The film grossed $3.3 million worldwide against a
production budget of nearly $1.5 million.
For their acting, Victor was nominated at the 83rd Golden Globe
Awards in Best Actress in a Motion Picture – Drama.
For their filmmaking, Victor won Best Directorial Debut from the National Board of Review and
was nominated for Best Original Screenplay at the 31st Critics' Choice Awards.
The film explores themes of rape, post-traumatic stress
disorder (ptsd), cat, professor, massachusetts.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.